Prophet T.B. Joshua stands in the authority and power of the name of Jesus Christ
as he sets the people free from bondage with a touch or a simple look from God
that exposes the darkness hidden inside them.
There is no hiding place for demons when Jesus is on the scene.
Let us hear from the evil spirit inside this woman.
I gave her the spirit of prostitution.
I want to destroy her life with the spirit of prostitution.
I sleep with between 10 to 30 men - it depends.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
How did you enter her?
After she had finished with her school.
Knowing that the demon has been chained by the power of God.
Thank You, Jesus!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
My name is Nkechi Uwaifo. I am from Delta state.
The person beside me here is my mother.
The next person here is my elder
sister; her name is Justina.
The one near me is Faith, and the other one is Angela.
They are all my elder sisters.
What brought me to The SCOAN was the spirit of prostitution.
When I was in school, somebody came to deceive us.
I wanted to write my exams in SS3 (Senior Secondary School).
Somebody came and deceived us
that she wanted to take us to La Cote d' Ivoire.
There were 10 of us.
How old were you at that time?
By that time I was thirteen years.
And you were in what class?
I was going to a SS3 (Senior Secondary School).
So the person came and told us that she wanted to take us to La Cote d'Ivoire
and that there, we would continue our schooling.
When we got to La Cote d'Ivoire, she introduced us into prostitution.
She didn't tell us when we were in Nigeria hat she was taking us there to do prostitution.
When we got to La Cote d'Ivoire, she told us that we would be doing prostitution.
We had to pay the woman 400,000 CFA.
I told her that she did not tell us all these things when we were in Nigeria.
She said that we didn't have sense;
that didn't we see that many people were making money and building houses everywhere
and that we didn't want to be millionaires?
Then, we said we would do it because we didn't have a choice.
From there, the woman took us to the madam.
The madam called us and talked to us that we should do it and that she too was doing it.
She said that she paid the person who brought her to La Cote d'Ivoire 400,000 CFA.
and that we were going to pay the same amount before we would be free and on our own.
When she explained it to us like that, we said that we would do it.
When we started doing it in La Cote d'Ivoire, we started paying her the money.
I took four months to pay her the 400,000 CFA.
Sometimes, I slept with 10 to 20 men; it depended on when there were customers.
After that, she said that we should have our own place and she would rent a place for us.
We too should have our own place to do our own thing and begin to gather money
to start what we would be doing in life.
When she explained this to us, we told her no problem.
She rented a place for us and we started doing our own.
Then, we started gathering our own money.
For more than 8 years, I did not hear anything from my family.
Your family members were not aware that you had travelled?
Yes.
You didn't tell anyone?
No, I didn't tell them.
I went to the person that brought me to La Cote d'Ivoire that I wanted to hear from my family.
He said that I should not worry and that he would get the number
for me.
He said that I should call my family but I should not tell them what I was doing in La Cote d'Ivoire.
He told me that I should lie to my family.
I agreed that I would speak to my family like that because they didn't know what I was doing.
I called my mother and she said that they had been looking for me for so many years.
When I told her I was in La Cote d'Ivoire, she asked me what I was doing there.
I told her that I was learning how to plait hair.
Another day, when I called them, they would ask if I was still plaiting hair in La Cote d'Ivoire.
I would say yes but I was lying to them.
Sometime later, they would call me again and I would lie to them that I was sewing.
I continued lying to them, telling them different types of stories.
So for how many years did you say your family did not see you?
For eight years.
You were in La Cote d'Ivoire doing the work of prostitution?
Yes!
Okay, so what happened after that?
When I gathered my money, I went to Morocco; I said I wanted to travel to Spain
On my way to Spain, I got deported from Morocco to Mali.
In Mali, I started doing prostitution again to gather money to get to Spain.
When I had gathered enough money, I tried to get to Spain again.
But on my way to Spain, they deported me again; this made it two times now.
I came back to La Cote d'Ivoire again.
What were you planning to do to Spain?
It was the same prostitution.
Okay, so now you were deported twice from Spain back to La Cote d'Ivoire?
Yes.
So what happened after that?
I met the father of my child.
This child here - Blessing.
He told me that he liked me and he wanted to marry me.
I said, okay, there was no problem and we started befriending each other.
Then, I got pregnant.
He told me that since for eight years, I had not seen my family,
he would like to follow me to go and see them.
From there, he started seeing my family and introduced himself as the father of my pregnancy
and that he wanted to marry me.
We then travelled to Warri in Delta State to his mother's place; he introduced me to his mother.
His mother told me that I should stay in her place to deliver my baby.
I said, "No problem, Mama. I will stay".
I told her that I didn't have any money to do any business in Nigeria.
She said that I shouldn't worry and that her son would send money for me.
I told her that I had money in the bank account of the father of my child.
I had money with him in his account.
I said that she should let him send the money to me for me to start business in Nigeria
as I didn't want to return to La Cote d' Ivoire anymore; I was tired.
The father of this child told me that I should not worry and that the money that was in the bank,
that the bank wanted to borrow the money and put interest on it for me
so that at the end of the year, the bank would gather all the money together for me.
I had gathered 1 million CFA by that time in La Cote d' Ivoire.
Out of the work of prostitution, you were able to gather that money?
Yes,
{So eventually, what now happened with the money?
The man was just telling me stories and until today, I have not seen the money.
I had to forget about the money.
So you mean he duped you?
Yes.
I just thought that as he had promised that he wanted to marry me, no problem.
I knew that through that promise he made, if he had money,
he would give me the money that was in his account back.
Then, I was pregnant with this girl.
At that time, I was still doing prostitution.
After having this child, I stopped doing prostitution.
After eight years, when you came back home, did your family accept you ?
Yes, they accepted me but I still went back to the father of my child.
I told them that I was going to Warri to go and deliver my child.
From there, after you delivered your child, what happened?
I delivered twins but they did not live.
Before this one?
Yes.
Then, he called me and said that I should come back to La Cote d' Ivoire.
I didn't know that he was just deceiving me to use my money.
So you still found yourself back to La Cote d' Ivoire?
Yes
Doing what?
I was doing the same prostitution.
When this child was one year old, I came back to Nigeria for her to know my family.
My family did not know about this child.
Since I came back with this child, I did not go back to La Cote d' Ivoire.
When I wanted to go back again, after my family had seen my child,
I went to meet the father of this child.
I said, "See what is happening; I don't have money for me to start again in Nigeria.
Nobody wants to help me".
Okay. Tell us how you eventually came here.
What happened? How did you come to The SCOAN? Who brought you here?
It was my mother who told me that I should come here for deliverance.
Okay, after eight years you went back again?
Yes,
So altogether, how many years were you doing this work?
That is 12 years.
Twelve years?
Yes.
For this 12 years, can you give an account of anything you acquired -
maybe money, property, car, house or anything that you were able to get
as a result of this work of prostitution.
Nothing!
Wow.
Both fathers of these children are not alive; I am the one taking care of these children.
because I still went back and struggled to have money to train these children
through doing prostitution here in Nigeria also.
Okay, can you now tell us how you came to The SCOAN.
It was my mother who introduced me to The SCOAN, that I should come for deliverance.
Okay, so when you came, what happened?
When I came that Monday, the man of God prayed for me.
When the man of God prayed for me, I just fell down.
The spirit inside me began to manifest that it wanted to make my life useless.
It confessed that it was the spirit of prostitution.
Then, he delivered me. Now, I am free and I thank God that I am free!
I am not going back again.
That night the man of God prayed for me, in a dream, I felt something come out
of the back of my head; I thought it was a rat.
I was surprised but I thought that a rat could not enter this house.
I slept and in another dream, I saw somebody with a giant hand touch me and I fell down.
That night, I woke up and started
praying.
I said, "God, this deliverance that I
have been waiting for, I have received it".
So that was before the man of God prayed for you?
The day the man of God touched me was the day that I had that dream.
Since after that time, can you tell us what happened.
I still had another dream.
I saw myself preaching to people who were doing prostitution.
I told them that they should not do
this work.
Leave that life, work and face God. God has solution.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So you could not imagine yourself, seeing yourself in the dream, preaching to people
who are doing the same work you were doing for 12 years - the work of prostitution.
Yes!
Apart from that, tell us: What are the changes you have noticed after your deliverance?
Do you still have the urge to go out and meet men, to run away from home, to travel out?
Do you still have such urge?
No. Now, if I sleep, I will sleep
like a baby and wake up.
I now dream good dreams for my life, even seeing myself praying but before, I did not pray.
If I said that I would pray, I would just go and sleep.
Sometimes, people would come to sleep with me; I'd be doing prostitution in the dream
but since the man of God delivered me, I have not seen that kind of thing again.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the king of glory!
We thank God Almighty for your life.
One more thing we would like to hear from you because people are listening to you,
they are learning from what you are saying.
Many people would have a reason for going out into such a job as prostitution -
maybe because of msltreatment from their parents, their family.
Was there any maltreatment from your family before you decided to travel out for this job?
Yes.
Back when I was small, I thought that my sisters and mother did not like me.
Sometimes, I thought that they hated me.
That was why when I went to Agbor, that spirit that influenced me to travel was able to enter me.
Okay. Once again, let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
My name is Grace Uwaifo. I am from Delta State.
She is my daughter Nkechi; the rest are her elder sisters.
I thank God for her life.
Two weeks ago, when she came here, she received her deliverance.
Before then, she always cried, telling me she wanted to go back to La Cote d'Ivoire.
One day, when I came home, she would have killed herself or gone back to La Cote d'Ivoire.
I would tell her, "No. One day God will deliver you from this spirit".
because I knew that it was not ordinary.
She came to collect money for WECC and NECO exams.
She used the money to travel out and
for eight years, nobody heard about her.
It was eight years.
Then, she came and went back for four years before she came back with this baby.
Okay. We thank God Almighty. So how do you feel now, seeing that your daughter is delivered?
I thank God for her deliverance. I am very happy.
Can we hear from one of the sisters.
Please tell us your name.
My name is Justina. I am from Delta State, Nigeria.
As a young child, I was sent on to further my education,
so no one was there to watch after her.
Coming across the wrong set of people was how she just began to waste her years.
Now, I believe that the past is over and the best is yet to come for her.
Thank you. Shall we clap for Jesus Christ.
Miss Nkechi Uwaifo & Family
Deliverance Testimony
My name is Faith Okonkwo.
I thank God for my life and for what He has done in my sister's life.
I thank God that she came back and was delivered.
I give God the glory; I give God the honour.
For how many years did you not seen her?
For 12 years.
Glory be to God.
My name is Gbadebo Angela.
I'm the elder sister to Nkechi.
I want to use this medium to appreciate God for deilvering my sister,
for bringing my sister safely back and alive after going astray.
I want to use this medium to advise the youth, most especially the young girls
that they should be content with what they have.
They should appreciate their families.
They should hold on to the Word of God and believe that their present condition
is not the final stage of their life; the best is yet to come.
If we pray, hold on to God and work hard, we will definitely get to where we want to go.
Amen. Thank you very much. Thank you.
Miss Nkechi Uwaifo & Family
Deliverance Testimony
My advice for the viewers, most especially to the young girls
and those who are doing this prostitution,
let them run to God who delivered me, for them to have their own deliverance.
That work is not a good work.
Thank you. Let us clap for Jesus Christ.
A word is enough for the wise, so we thank God Almighty for your life once again.
Now that you are delivered, we want to
encourage you to stay true to our Lord Jesus Christ,
to embrace the wonderful Word of God as the most effective instrument for change.
Now the spirit of prostitution has been cast out, you need to build the character of God
and this can only happen by making the Word of God the standard for your life.
We pray that the Lord Almighty will give you the grace
to make the Word of God the standard for your life, in Jesus' name.
We believe that this deliverance will bring total deliverance to the entire family, in Jesus' name.
Thank You, Jesus. Let us clap for Jesus one more time.
Miss Nkechi Uwaifo & Family
Deliverance Testimony
After the service, the Emmanuel TV team met up with Nkechi Uwaifo and her family once again
to hear their thoughts on the next step for the family in the light of her wonderful deliverance.
STANDARD FOR LIFE
Emmanuel, viewers! God is with us!
We thank God for everything that the Lord God Almighty has done in this service today.
In the course of the service today, while the testimonies were going on,
we saw our sister here who came with her family members to share the testimony
of her deliverance from her past life of prostitution.
Today, she's a new person in Christ Jesus and she's here with her family right now
to say what is the next plan after her
deliverance and her testimony today.
So sister, once again, can you tell us your name and of those who are standing with you.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Nkechi Uwaifo from Delta State.
These are my elder sisters and my mother.
I thank God for what He has done for me,
using the man of God to deliver me from my past life of prostitution.
I pray to Almighty God that I will never go back to my past life again.
I will serve God in truth and in spirit.
We thank God Almighty for everything. So you mean, now that you are delivered
and you have shared the testimony of your deliverance,
you're going back to start a new life and not going back to your old way of life, is that right?
Yes, I promise God.
Let us also hear from members of your family
because we believe now that they have accepted you back,
they also understand that they have a role to play
to make sure that this deliverance is maintained.
So sister, once again tell us your name.
My name is Justina
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I want to thank God for what happened today in the life of my sister.
I give God all the glory.
We promise to support her in any way we can.
My husband and I have decided to take care of the little girl
so that Nkechi can start her life all over again.
I will support her in any way I can so that she can get her life back.
Everyone makes mistakes; we believe she has made a mistake and has learnt from it.
She is going to start her life afresh and I know God has plans for her.
Every one of us will contribute in trying to see that she gets back on her feet.
Thank you very much.
We thank God Almighty. That is the love that our Lord Jesus Christ has been preaching
that we should learn to forgive one another and also to help one another's weakness.
Okay. Our dear sister, now that your past is over
and you have shared your testimony today before the congregation,
the anointed man of God, together with the Emmanuel TV partners, wants to support you
so that you can start a new life.
That is, choose whatever business you want to go into
so that you will not have any cause to remember and go back to your old way of life of prostitution.
In view of this, the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, together with the Emmanuel TV partners,
has sent this 200,000 Naira for you to start something doing and take care of yourself.
We believe that God Almighty will continue the supply.
Also in addition, we have 'The Mirror' book and this is also to help you
to maintain the deliverance you have received.
That is the Word of God that is authored by the anointed man of God himself, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I thank God for what He has done for using the man of God
to give me this opportunity to start a new life.
I pray to Almighty God that in my next visit here,
I am going to testify of glory and
honour for all that God has done for me, in Jesus' name.
I thank you, Man of God, for what you have done; you will never lack in your life or your family.
Long life will be your portion, in Jesus' name!
Thank you to the Emmanuel TV partners.
I pray to Almighty God: May God guide the Emmanuel TV partners,
long life and prosperity, in Jesus' name.
I want to say a very big thank you to the great man of God and Emmanuel TV partners.
I want to thank you for your love and support, both morally and financially.
I pray the good Lord will attend to every one of our needs, in Jesus' name.
I thank God. My children have said it all.
I thank God, the man of God and Emmanuel TV partners.
I thank them; may God continue to bless them
I pray for more grace for the man of God - more grace, anointing
and strength to continue his work.
God bless the man of God.
I want to say I thank God for what
He has done in my sister's life.
We give all the glory, we give all the honour to God.
Father, we thank you.
May your name be glorified, in Jesus' name. Amen.
I will support her in any way, in the name of Jesus.
I am really grateful for a day like this.
I have prayed for a day like this and I thank God that it came to pass.
I want to use this medium to thank the Emmanuel TV partners.
For Prophet T.B. Joshua, I pray for more anointing upon his life.
I pray for strength to carry on the work of the Lord
and I pray that God will strengthen and protect him.
God will protect Emmanuel TV partners.
Whatsoever be their hearts' desires all over the world, I pray that God will grant them.
Wherever this money has come from, the source will never run dry in Jesus' name.
For my sister, I pray that God will sustain her, maintain this deliverance - it shall be permanent,
Every power that wants to take her back to her past
is hereby condemned today, in the name of Jesus Christ.
I pray I will support her in every way I can, for her to be saved forever, in Jesus' name.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Thank you very much.
Now that it is all over, we want to see that love being well expressed.
With what God has blessed her with, very soon, we believe that our sister is coming back
to share a testimony of the breakthrough that will come out
of this wonderful gesture she has received today, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Miss Nkechi Uwaifo Receives 200,000 Naira
From T.B. Joshua And Emmanuel TV Partners
TT: Lizz Ndung'u 04:08:2018
RV: Mel Flowers 29/08/2018